STRESS-PASS STRESS-DET repeat identical seq0
STRESS-PASS STRESS-DET dual-core agree seq0
STRESS-PASS STRESS-DET repeat identical seq1
STRESS-PASS STRESS-DET dual-core agree seq1
STRESS-PASS STRESS-DET repeat identical seq2
STRESS-PASS STRESS-DET dual-core agree seq2
STRESS-PERF 200 accesses n=64: 0.00s
STRESS-PASS STRESS-PERF under 30s
STRESS-PASS STRESS-IDEM freeze deterministic
STRESS-PASS STRESS-IDEM freeze matches sealed file
[WP0-STEP-01] terminal claim exact: FINITE_DEBT_LAW_MINING_RESULTS
[WP0-STEP-01] parent_contract carries full commit + seal hashes
[WP0-STEP-01] PARENT-04 firewall pristine: EMPTY
[WP0-STEP-01] PARENT-05 firewall pristine: BANK_COMMITTED
STRESS-PASS STRESS-MUT tampered seal fails
[WP0-STEP-01] parent commit exact: 38c1be6afd2ab2420aa094c68ce45ee6a26b3628
[WP0-STEP-01] terminal claim exact: FINITE_DEBT_LAW_MINING_RESULTS
[WP0-STEP-01] parent_contract carries full commit + seal hashes
[WP0-STEP-01] PARENT-04 firewall pristine: EMPTY
[WP0-STEP-01] PARENT-05 firewall pristine: BANK_COMMITTED
STRESS-PASS STRESS-MUT restored seal passes
[WP0-STEP-05] ledger holds 26 obligations, all lifecycle-tracked
STRESS-PASS STRESS-MUT dropped obligation fails
[WP0-STEP-06] 27 translation objects preregistered (yaml self-declares count)
STRESS-PASS STRESS-MUT pre-resolved mapping fails
STRESS-PASS STRESS-MUT early science fails
[WP0-STEP-06] 27 translation objects preregistered (yaml self-declares count)
STRESS-PASS STRESS-MUT dropped fallback fails
STRESS-PASS STRESS-INV missing key raises
STRESS-PASS STRESS-INV cost missing key raises
STRESS-PASS STRESS-INV trace snapshot 64hex
STRESS-PASS STRESS-INV inorder preserved
STRESS-PASS STRESS-INV delete y=0
STRESS-PASS STRESS-STUB phase01 exit 2
STRESS-PASS STRESS-STUB phase01 says NOT_AUTHORIZED
STRESS-PASS STRESS-STUB phase09 exit 2
STRESS-PASS STRESS-STUB phase09 says NOT_AUTHORIZED
STRESS-PASS STRESS-STUB phase19 exit 2
STRESS-PASS STRESS-STUB phase19 says NOT_AUTHORIZED
STRESS-FAILURES: none
